http://www.burnfund.org/privacy-policy

This is the subscribe section
The British Columbia Professional Fire Fighters’ Burn Fund is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information collected on this site in accordance with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Document Act (PIPEDA) and the British Columbia Personal Information Protection Act (PIPA).
The British Columbia Professional Fire Fighters’ Burn Fund collects information from users through online donations, Burn Fund Link subscription requests and online merchandise sales.
Use of information
The Burn Fund is firmly committed to data privacy, particularly as it relates to visitors to this website. We do not sell, rent or exchange any personal information collected from our site visitors that has been gathered online.
We do send email notifications of events, news, bulletins, updates in addition to e-receipts, requests for support and acknowledgements of donations. Every mass e-mail we send our supporters has an unsubscribe feature. You may ‘opt-out’ from receiving e-communications at any time by utilizing the unsubscribe feature embedded in the email. You may also request to be excluded from receiving certain communications by contacting us by phone or by email.
Security and Confidentiality
All online transactions and contributions on this site occur through a safe, private, and secure system that protects the user’s personal information.
Links to external sites
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that the British Columbia Professional Fire Fighters’ Burn Fund is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users, when leaving our site, to read the privacy policy of every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
